Finding Aid for the Robert A. McGaw Map Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- A New Map of Tennessee With Its Roads and Distances, 1841; 58; ID: 58 Map #: 057 Map Title: A New Map of Tennessee With Its Roads and Distances Date of Creation: 1841 Cartographer: H.S. Tanner Engraver: J. and W.W. Warr Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: H.S. Tanner Source of Information: Tanner's "Universal Atlas" Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 10.5x14.5 Notes: Insets of Nashville and Knoxville. Includes table to Steam Boat Routes Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Sixth Geological Report to the Twenty-Fourth General Assembly of the State of Tennessee, 1841; 59; ID: 59 Map #: 058 Map Title: Sixth Geological Report to the Twenty-Fourth General Assembly of the State of Tennessee Date of Creation: 1841 Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Nashville Publisher: C.C. Norvell and W.F. Bang and Co. Source of Information: Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 8.5x5.5 Notes: Includes Geological Map of Sevier County by G. Troost. Author: Gerard Troost. Housed in a folder. Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Neuste Karte von Tennessee, 1845; 60; ID: 60 Map #: 059 Map Title: Neuste Karte von Tennessee Date of Creation: 1845 Cartographer: Maasstaebe Engraver: Instituts zu Hildburghausen Place of Publication: Amsterdam Publisher: Source of Information: Meyer's "Handatlas" Color/Black and White: some color Size of Map: 12x14.5 Notes: Insets of Nashville and Knoxville. Mounted on linen. Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Die Colonie Neu- Bamberg im Staate Tennessee in Nord Amerika, 1846; 61; ID: 61 Map #: 060 Map Title: Die Colonie Neu- Bamberg im Staate Tennessee in Nord Amerika Date of Creation: 1846 Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Baumberg, Germany Publisher: Drud und Berlag des Literarifich and Artifchen Instituts Source of Information: Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 7x4.5 Notes: Pamphlet relating to a proposed colony near where Dickson, Tennessee stands. Housed in a folder. Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- A New Map of Tennessee, [1847]; 62; ID: 62 Map #: 061 Map Title: A New Map of Tennessee Date of Creation: [1847] Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: S. Augustus Mitchell Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 11x15 Notes: Shows stage and steam boat routes. Insets of Environs of Nashville and Knoxville. Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- A New Map of Tennessee, 1849; 63; ID: 63 Map #: 062 Map Title: A New Map of Tennessee Date of Creation: 1849 Cartographer: S. Augustus Mitchell Engraver: Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: Notes: Framed: Yes Location: Foyer
- A New Map of Tennessee With Its Roads and Distances, 1850; 64; ID: 64 Map #: 063 Map Title: A New Map of Tennessee With Its Roads and Distances Date of Creation: 1850 Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Publisher: Thomas, Cowperthwait and Co. Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 11.25x15.25 Notes: Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Map of Cumberland and Franklin, [1853]; 65; ID: 65 Map #: 064 Map Title: Map of Cumberland and Franklin Date of Creation: [1853] Cartographer: Engraver: W. Keenan Place of Publication: Charleston, S.C. Publisher: Walker and James Source of Information: J.G.M. Ramsey's "Annals of Tennessee" Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 8x17 Notes: Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Kentucky and Tennessee, [1855]; 66; ID: 66 Map #: 065 Map Title: Kentucky and Tennessee Date of Creation: [1855] Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: New York Publisher: J.H. Colton and Co. Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 11.5x16.5 Notes: Framed: Yes Location: Foyer
- County Map of Kentucky and Tennessee, 1860; 67; ID: 67 Map #: 066 Map Title: County Map of Kentucky and Tennessee Date of Creation: 1860 Cartographer: S. Augustus Mitchell, Jr. Engraver: Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 10.75x13.25 Notes: Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- A New Map of Tennessee With Its Roads and Distances, 1860; 68; ID: 68 Map #: 067 Map Title: A New Map of Tennessee With Its Roads and Distances Date of Creation: 1860 Cartographer: Charles Desilver Engraver: Place of Publication: Publisher: Charles Desilver Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 11.5x15.5 Notes: Insets of Nashville and Knoxville Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Nashville City and Business Directory, for 1860-1861, 69; ID: 69 Map #: 068 Map Title: Nashville City and Business Directory, for 1860-1861 Date of Creation: 1860 Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Nashville Publisher: L.P. Williams and Co. Source of Information: Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 9x6 Notes: Includes black and white street map of Nashville. Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Panorama of the Seat of War. Bird's Eye View of Kentucky and Tennessee Showing Cairo and Part of the Southern States, 1861; 70; ID: 70 Map #: 069 Map Title: Panorama of the Seat of War. Bird's Eye View of Kentucky and Tennessee Showing Cairo and Part of the Southern States Date of Creation: 1861 Cartographer: John Bachmann Engraver: John Bachmann Place of Publication: New York Publisher: John Bachmann Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 16.5x28.25 Notes: Tables showing distance from Cairo to several locations. Panorama showing rivers, cities, forts and landscapes. Framed: No Location: Missing
- Plan of Fort Henry, Tenn., [1862]; 71; ID: 71 Map #: 070 Map Title: Plan of Fort Henry, Tenn. Date of Creation: [1862] Cartographer: Alex Simplot Engraver: Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 6x9.75 Notes: Pencil- sketch of "Secession Ordinance Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Map of Middle Tennessee, 1863; 72; ID: 72 Map #: 071 Map Title: Map of Middle Tennessee Date of Creation: 1863 Cartographer: Edward B. Sayers Engraver: Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 12.5x24 Notes: Ink on oilcloth. Shows Confederate signal stations, depots, etcand#8230; from Franklin to Shelbyville. Sayers was Captain and Chief Engineer, Polk's Corps, CSA. Map was drawn at Hdqtrs. Engineer's Dept. Shelbyville, May 6, 1863. Framed: No Location: Missing
- Civil War Map of Area Around Shiloh and Corinth, Mississippi, [1863]; 73; ID: 73 Map #: 072 Map Title: Civil War Map of Area Around Shiloh and Corinth, Mississippi Date of Creation: [1863] Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 3.75x6.5 Notes: Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Rough Plan of part of Battle of Waukatchie, Tenn., 1863; 74; ID: 74 Map #: 073 Map Title: Rough Plan of part of Battle of Waukatchie, Tenn. Date of Creation: 1863 Cartographer: H.T. Engraver: Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 8x12.25 Notes: Drawn from memory by H.T., presumably a Union soldier. Framed: No Location: Missing
- Map of Northern Georgia and Tennessee, 1863; 75; ID: 75 Map #: 074 Map Title: Map of Northern Georgia and Tennessee Date of Creation: 1863 Cartographer: Engraver: J.T. Paterson Place of Publication: Augusta, Georgia Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: some color Size of Map: 16x23 Notes: Inset of Chattanooga and vicinity. Confederate imprint. Framed: No Location: Missing
- Johnson's Kentucky and Tennessee, 1865; 76; ID: 76 Map #: 075 Map Title: Johnson's Kentucky and Tennessee Date of Creation: 1865 Cartographer: Alvin J. Johnson Engraver: Place of Publication: New York Publisher: Alvin J. Johnson and Co. Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 17.25x23 Notes: Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- County Map of Kentucky and Tennessee, 1867; 77; ID: 77 Map #: 076 Map Title: County Map of Kentucky and Tennessee Date of Creation: 1867 Cartographer: S. Augustus Mitchell, Jr. Engraver: Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 10.5x13.5 Notes: Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Map of The State of Kentucky and Part of Tennessee, ca. 1869; 78; ID: 78 Map #: 077 Map Title: Map of The State of Kentucky and Part of Tennessee Date of Creation: ca. 1869 Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 7x10.5 Notes: Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Geological Map of Tennessee, 1869; 79; ID: 79 Map #: 078 Map Title: Geological Map of Tennessee Date of Creation: 1869 Cartographer: J.M. Safford Engraver: Ferd. Mayer and Sons Place of Publication: New York Publisher: Taintor Brothers Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 14x47 Notes: Framed: No Location: Missing
- Colton's map of the State of Tennessee 1870, ca. 1866; 80; ID: 80 Map #: 079 Map Title: Colton's map of the State of Tennessee 1870 Date of Creation: ca. 1866 Cartographer: G.W. and C.B. Colton Engraver: Place of Publication: New York Publisher: G.W. and C.B. Colton and Co. Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 19.25x23.75 Notes: In two parts Framed: No Location: Bottom Drawer
- Kentucky and Tennessee, undated; 81; ID: 81 Map #: 080 Map Title: Kentucky and Tennessee Date of Creation: undated Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 5x7 Notes: Map was drawn in the post-Civil War period Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Gray's New Map of Kentycky and Tennessee, [1876]; 82; ID: 82 Map #: 081 Map Title: Gray's New Map of Kentycky and Tennessee Date of Creation: [1876] Cartographer: Frank A. Gray Engraver: Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: O.W. Gray and Son Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 15.75x26 Notes: Insets showing system of railroads, comparative increases in population, hypsometric sketck of the two states, and density of population. Reverse side shows maps of Cincinnati, Indianapolis and Louisville Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Special Report on The Coal-Field of Little Sequatchie, 1876; 83; ID: 83 Map #: 082 Map Title: Special Report on The Coal-Field of Little Sequatchie Date of Creation: 1876 Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Nashville Publisher: tavel, Eastman and Howell Source of Information: Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 8x5.25 Notes: Author of pamphlet is J.B. Killebrew. Includes map of the Little Sequatchie Coalfields Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Map of Nashville and Vicinity, 1877; 84; ID: 84 Map #: 083 Map Title: Map of Nashville and Vicinity Date of Creation: 1877 Cartographer: W.F. Foster Engraver: Place of Publication: Nashville Publisher: tavel, Eastman and Howell Source of Information: Color/Black and White: outline color Size of Map: 19.75x23.75 Notes: Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Middle Tennessee as an Iron Center, 1879; 85; ID: 85 Map #: 084 Map Title: Middle Tennessee as an Iron Center Date of Creation: 1879 Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Nashville Publisher: Tavel, Eastman and Howell Source of Information: Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 8.5x5.75 Notes: Author is J.B. Killebrew. Includes map of iron deposits. Killebrew was Commissioner of Agriculture, Statistics and Mines and Immigration, for the State of Tennessee Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Map Showing Part of the Iron Field West of Nashville, ca. 1879; 86; ID: 86 Map #: 085 Map Title: Map Showing Part of the Iron Field West of Nashville Date of Creation: ca. 1879 Cartographer: J.B. Killebrew Engraver: Louisville Lithographing Co. Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: some color Size of Map: 14.5x21 Notes: Killebrew was Commissioner of Agriculture Framed: No Location: Missing
- Nashville, ca. 1880; 87; ID: 87 Map #: 086 Map Title: Nashville Date of Creation: ca. 1880 Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: some color Size of Map: 13x10 Notes: Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Biennial Report of the President of Fire and Police Commissioners of the Taxing District (Memphis) Shelby County, Tennessee, to the Governor of The State, 1880; 88; ID: 88 Map #: 087 Map Title: Biennial Report of the President of Fire and Police Commissioners of the Taxing District (Memphis) Shelby County, Tennessee, to the Governor of The State Date of Creation: 1880 Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Memphis Publisher: S.C. Toof and Co. Source of Information: Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 9x5.75 Notes: Includes street map of Memphis Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Triangulation and Reconnaissance in Tennessee, 1881; 89; ID: 89 Map #: 088 Map Title: Triangulation and Reconnaissance in Tennessee Date of Creation: 1881 Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: "Coast and Geodetic Survey Reports for 1880 and 1881", no. 27 Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 10x16 Notes: Framed: No Location: Missing
- County Map of Kentucky and Tennessee, 1882; 90; ID: 90 Map #: 089 Map Title: County Map of Kentucky and Tennessee Date of Creation: 1882 Cartographer: S. Augustus Mitchell Engraver: W.H. Gamble Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: Notes: Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Railroad and County Map of Kentucky and Tennessee, 1882; 91; ID: 91 Map #: 090 Map Title: Railroad and County Map of Kentucky and Tennessee Date of Creation: 1882 Cartographer: Engraver: George F. Cram Place of Publication: Chicago Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: outline color Size of Map: 15.5x21.5 Notes: Framed: No Location: Missing
- Johnson's Kentucky and Tennessee, [1882]; 92; ID: 92 Map #: 091 Map Title: Johnson's Kentucky and Tennessee Date of Creation: [1882] Cartographer: Johnson and Ward Engraver: Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 16.5x24 Notes: Insets showing engraved sketches of the State Capitol, the Memphis Navy Yard, and the Entrance to the Mammoth Cave Framed: Yes Location: Foyer
- County Map of Kentucky and Tennessee, 1884; 93; ID: 93 Map #: 092 Map Title: County Map of Kentucky and Tennessee Date of Creation: 1884 Cartographer: S Augustus Mitchell Engraver: W.H. Gambel Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 13x20.5 Notes: Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Map of the Former Territorial Limits of the Cherokee "Nation of" Indians, 1884; 94; ID: 94 Map #: 093 Map Title: Map of the Former Territorial Limits of the Cherokee "Nation of" Indians Date of Creation: 1884 Cartographer: C.C. Royce Engraver: N. Peters Place of Publication: Washington D.C. Publisher: Smithsonian Institution Source of Information: "5th. Annual Report, Smithsonian Institution Bureau of Ethnology" Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 28.25x31.5 Notes: Includes table showing Numeric and Chronologic Schedules of Cherokee Cessions Framed: No Location: Bottom Drawer
- Plan of the City of Nashville and Vicinity, ca. 1885; 95; ID: 95 Map #: 094 Map Title: Plan of the City of Nashville and Vicinity Date of Creation: ca. 1885 Cartographer: W.F. Foster Engraver: Ehrgott and Krebs Place of Publication: Cincinnati Publisher: E.D. King Source of Information: Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 18x26 Notes: Framed: No Location: Bottom Drawer
- Nashville, Tenn. 1888 Looking North West, 96; ID: 96 Map #: 095 Map Title: Nashville, Tenn. 1888 Looking North West Date of Creation: 1888 Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Milwaukee Publisher: H. Wellege and Co. Source of Information: Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 25x38.25 Notes: Panorama showing individual buildings, many of which are identified at bottom. Insets show Nashville Iron, Steel and Charcoal Co.; National Manufacturing Co.; Tennessee Range and Manufacturing Co.; West Nashville; D.H. Baldwin and Co. Pianos and Organs Framed: Yes Location: Foyer
- Kimball, Marion County Tennessee, ca. 1890; 97; ID: 97 Map #: 096 Map Title: Kimball, Marion County Tennessee Date of Creation: ca. 1890 Cartographer: Nathan F. Barrett Engraver: N.Y. Engraving and Printing Co. Place of Publication: New York Publisher: Kimball Town Company Source of Information: Color/Black and White: some color Size of Map: 34x27 Notes: From survey of W.T. and A.S. Kelley, Civil Engineers. Includes engraved sketch of the Angle Court Hotel. A large town plan for the proposed town of Kimball Framed: No Location: Bottom Drawer
- The Town of Cardiff, 1890; 98; ID: 98 Map #: 097 Map Title: The Town of Cardiff Date of Creation: 1890 Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Boston Publisher: Heliotype Printing Co. Source of Information: Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 9.25x6 Notes: Pamphlet promoting a proposed twon in East Tennessee Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Defenses of Nashville1864, 1865, [1892]; 99; ID: 99 Map #: 098 Map Title: Defenses of Nashville1864, 1865 Date of Creation: [1892] Cartographer: Office of the Inspector General of Fortifications, Z.B. Tower, U.S. Engineers, Military Division of Mississippi Engraver: Julius Bien and Co. Place of Publication: New York Publisher: Source of Information: "Atlas to Accompany the Official Records of the Union and Confederate Armies, 1861-1865" Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 16.5x27.5 Notes: Shows defense plans for Battery Erwin, Battery Coolidge, Battery for Casino Hill, the Capitol, Fort Dan McCook, Fort Morton, Fort Sill, Fort W.D. Whipple, and Redoubt for Hill No. 210 Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Kentucky and Tennessee, 100; ID: 100 Map #: 099 Map Title: Kentucky and Tennessee Date of Creation: Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 10.5x12.5 Notes: Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Map of Nashville: Guide to the City, ca. 1915; 101; ID: 101 Map #: 100 Map Title: Map of Nashville: Guide to the City Date of Creation: ca. 1915 Cartographer: Nashville Railway and Light Co. Engraver: Place of Publication: Nashville Publisher: Zibart Brothers Source of Information: Color/Black and White: Size of Map: Notes: Framed: No Location: Missing
- Soil Survey of Dickson County Tennessee, 1926; 102; ID: 102 Map #: 101 Map Title: Soil Survey of Dickson County Tennessee Date of Creation: 1926 Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Washington D.C. Publisher: U.S. Department of Agriculture Bureau of Soils in Cooperation With the Tennessee Geological Survey Source of Information: Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 6.25x6 Notes: Authors are J.A. Kerr, H.G. Lewis, W.J. Latimer and E.H. Bailey Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Soil Map of Tennessee Dickson County Sheet, 1923; 103; ID: 103 Map #: 101a Map Title: Soil Map of Tennessee Dickson County Sheet Date of Creation: 1923 Cartographer: J.A. Kerr, H.G. Lewis, W.J. Latimer, E.H. Bailey Engraver: Williams- Webb Co. Place of Publication: Washington D.C. Publisher: U.S. Department of Agriculture Bureau of Soils in Cooperation with the Tennessee Geological Survey Source of Information: "Soil Survey of Dickson County, Tennessee" Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 26.25x24.25 Notes: Soil Survey of Dickson County, Tennessee is also in collection (no. 101) Framed: No Location: Bottom Drawer
- Complete Map of Nashville Wards and Suburbs, undated; 104; ID: 104 Map #: 102 Map Title: Complete Map of Nashville Wards and Suburbs Date of Creation: undated Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Nashville Publisher: Jersey Farms Milk Service Source of Information: Color/Black and White: some color Size of Map: 39x39 Notes: Mid- Twentieth century. Street names are indexed Framed: No Location: Bottom Drawer
- Southern Provinces of The United States, 105; ID: 105 Map #: 103 Map Title: Southern Provinces of The United States Date of Creation: Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: Thomason's "New General Atlas" Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 19.25x23.25 Notes: Inset shows "Characteristic Scenery of the Hudson River." Georgia includes Alabama and Mississippi Framed: Yes Location: Foyer
- Eastern Cherokees in North Carolina. Letter from the Secretary of the Interior In Response to Resolution of The House, 1882; 106; ID: 106 Map #: 104 Map Title: Eastern Cherokees in North Carolina. Letter from the Secretary of the Interior In Response to Resolution of The House Date of Creation: 1882 Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Government Printing Office Source of Information: Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 9x5.75 Notes: Author is H.M. Teller Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Agricultural and Geological Map of Tennessee, undated; 107; ID: 107 Map #: 105 Map Title: Agricultural and Geological Map of Tennessee Date of Creation: undated Cartographer: James M. Safford Engraver: Place of Publication: Nashville Publisher: Tavel, Eastman and Howell Source of Information: "Reports of the Bureau of Agriculture" Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 39.25x15.5 Notes: Shows topographic al features, railroads, county boundaries, county towns, etcand#8230; Framed: No Location: Bottom Drawer
- Map of the States of Kentucky and Tennessee, undated; 108; ID: 108 Map #: 106 Map Title: Map of the States of Kentucky and Tennessee Date of Creation: undated Cartographer: Engraver: Genner Sears and Co. Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 9.75x15.5 Notes: Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Map Prepared to exhibit The Campaigns in which The Army of the Cumberland Took Part During The War of The Rebellion, 1877; 109; ID: 109 Map #: 107 Map Title: Map Prepared to exhibit The Campaigns in which The Army of the Cumberland Took Part During The War of The Rebellion Date of Creation: 1877 Cartographer: Edward Ruger, A. Kilp and R. Flack Engraver: Julius Bien and Co. Place of Publication: New York Publisher: Source of Information: "Atlas to Accompany the Official Records of the Union and Confederate Armies, 1861-1865" Color/Black and White: some color Size of Map: 16.25x27.25 Notes: Includes maps illustrating the operations of the 7th Division at Cumberland Gap and the Environs of Petersburg, Va. Framed: No Location: Bottom Drawer
- Plan of Fort Des Ecores at Margot, undated; 110; ID: 110 Map #: 108 Map Title: Plan of Fort Des Ecores at Margot Date of Creation: undated Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 7.75x10.75 Notes: Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Eastern Cherokees in North Carolina, 1882; 111; ID: 111 Map #: A Map Title: Eastern Cherokees in North Carolina Date of Creation: 1882 Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Government Printing Office Source of Information: "House of Representatives Executive Document 196" Color/Black and White: Size of Map: Notes: Contains maps of Cherokee reservations in North Carolina Framed: No Location: Missing